{
  "listado": [
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Lionel|Messi",
      "pregunta": "1",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Cristiano|Ronaldo",
      "pregunta": "2",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Ronaldo",
      "pregunta": "3",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "diego|maradona",
      "pregunta": "4",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "enzo|francescoli",
      "pregunta": "5",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "zinedine|zidane",
      "pregunta": "6",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "raul",
      "pregunta": "7",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "pele",
      "pregunta": "8",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Zlatan|Ibrahimovic",
      "pregunta": "9",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "wayne|rooney",
      "pregunta": "10",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Franz|Beckenbauer",
      "pregunta": "11",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Johan|Cruyff",
      "pregunta": "12",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "rafa|marquez",
      "pregunta": "13",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "gohan",
      "pregunta": "14",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el gavilan|pollero",
      "pregunta": "15",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Kearney",
      "pregunta": "16",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "jefe|Quimby",
      "pregunta": "17",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "majin boo",
      "pregunta": "18",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "astro",
      "pregunta": "19",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|fortachon",
      "pregunta": "20",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "porky",
      "pregunta": "21",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "dr hibbert",
      "pregunta": "22",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "donald",
      "pregunta": "23",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "steve|Hyuga",
      "pregunta": "24",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "milhouse",
      "pregunta": "25",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "pluto",
      "pregunta": "26",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "lisa|simpson",
      "pregunta": "27",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "tiro loco|mcgraw",
      "pregunta": "28",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "akira",
      "pregunta": "29",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "robotina",
      "pregunta": "30",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "masha|y oso",
      "pregunta": "31",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "maggie|simpson",
      "pregunta": "32",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "super|sonico",
      "pregunta": "33",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "alcalde|diamante",
      "pregunta": "34",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "goofy",
      "pregunta": "35",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "huckleberry|hound",
      "pregunta": "36",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "la hormiga",
      "pregunta": "37",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el pajaro|loco",
      "pregunta": "38",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el inspector",
      "pregunta": "39",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el fantasma|del espacio",
      "pregunta": "40",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|vanidoso",
      "pregunta": "41",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "los gemelos|fantasticos",
      "pregunta": "42",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "artie|ziff",
      "pregunta": "43",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "ayudante|de santa",
      "pregunta": "44",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "carl|carlson",
      "pregunta": "45",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "cleto",
      "pregunta": "46",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "uter",
      "pregunta": "47",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "edna|krabappel",
      "pregunta": "48",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "barney",
      "pregunta": "49",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "patan",
      "pregunta": "50",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "jeremias|springfield",
      "pregunta": "51",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "jessica|alegria",
      "pregunta": "52",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "kent|brockman",
      "pregunta": "53",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "kirk|van houten",
      "pregunta": "54",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "margo|zavala",
      "pregunta": "55",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "montgomery|burns",
      "pregunta": "56",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "la mujer|maravilla",
      "pregunta": "57",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "profesor|frink",
      "pregunta": "58",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "rafa|gorgory",
      "pregunta": "59",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "cometin|sonico",
      "pregunta": "60",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "sam|bigotes",
      "pregunta": "61",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "leon o",
      "pregunta": "62",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "astroboy",
      "pregunta": "63",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "la hormiga|atomica",
      "pregunta": "64",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el oso|yogi",
      "pregunta": "65",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "jem",
      "pregunta": "66",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "herbert|powell",
      "pregunta": "67",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "benito",
      "pregunta": "68",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "la pantera|rosa",
      "pregunta": "69",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "funzo",
      "pregunta": "70",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "ricky|ricon",
      "pregunta": "71",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "duffman",
      "pregunta": "72",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "pikachu",
      "pregunta": "73",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "lucero|sonico",
      "pregunta": "74",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "gaspar",
      "pregunta": "75",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "battle cat",
      "pregunta": "76",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "jefe|gorgory",
      "pregunta": "77",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "super|raton",
      "pregunta": "78",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "jimbo",
      "pregunta": "79",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "juan|topo",
      "pregunta": "80",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "frank|grimes",
      "pregunta": "81",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "don gato",
      "pregunta": "82",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "pitufo|filosofo",
      "pregunta": "83",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "dr nick",
      "pregunta": "84",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "birdman",
      "pregunta": "85",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "vegetta",
      "pregunta": "86",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "larry|burns",
      "pregunta": "87",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "inocencia|donoso",
      "pregunta": "88",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "rayo de|plata",
      "pregunta": "89",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "lionel|hutz",
      "pregunta": "90",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "kang",
      "pregunta": "91",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "krusty",
      "pregunta": "92",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el gallo|claudio",
      "pregunta": "93",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "heidi",
      "pregunta": "94",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el jardinero|willy",
      "pregunta": "95",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "papa|pitufo",
      "pregunta": "96",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "Ultra|sonico",
      "pregunta": "97",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "mr chispa",
      "pregunta": "98",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "el inspector|gadget",
      "pregunta": "99",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    },
    {
      "titulo": "Jugadores",
      "respuesta": "martin|prince",
      "pregunta": "100",
      "categoria": "Jugadores"
    }
  ]
}
